School life is monotonous.
Every morning I get out of bed and run my daily training regimen out on the grounds.
Once I get back to my room, I do some magic drills.
Zanoba keeps begging me to teach him how to make figures, but I've gotten pretty rusty in these last few years.
I need to practice some more first.
I eat breakfast and lunch with Zanoba.
The university offers cuisine from all over, and a lot of it suits my palate to a tea.
It still falls short of the Japanese cooking I remember, but there are more than enough similar dishes to keep me satisfied.
Alina Lise gets plenty of one-on-one time with her fellow students and goes out on the town at night for extracurriculars.
You gotta give it to her. Her stamina is impressive.
In the afternoons, I take beginner-level classes in Healing, Divine, and Barrier Magic.
Roxy taught me a little about barriers when she was my tutor, but at the time I was satisfied just to know they existed and more or less tuned out the rest.
So starting over from the beginning ought to be helpful.
After class, I head back to the library and research teleportation until it gets dark.
I've gone through a lot of books, but teleportation is considered a forbidden art, so it's rarely written about in detail, and never instructionally.
In fact, exploring the teleporter labyrinth the book Master Fitz told me about might be the best source on the subject.
I've worked out a daily routine, and I've finally begun to settle in.
But my unfettered Shogun of the night still refuses to be manly.
One might say he is extremely fettered.
Oh, Lord.
Oh.
Rudeus.
Do you mind if I join you?
Not at all. Here, I even saved the seat for you.
Please sit. It's wonderful to see you again.
Thank you very much.
I feel like this guy really gets me.
How's your research going?
It's a little hard to tell.
Is that a book on teleportation?
Indeed.
I had been looking into the disaster myself.
Someone I know went missing, too.
I'm sorry. That's awful. I don't know what else to say.
It's all right. As a matter of fact, I've recently confirmed that he's alive.
Oh, really? That's great.
Yes. I never got the chance to search for him personally, so it was quite a relief.
That being said, I, uh, if you don't mind. And this is just a suggestion.
What is it?
I would like you to let me help with your research into the displacement incident.
I'm often busy, though. So I could only pop in occasionally. But if that doesn't bother you...
That's fine, of course. I'd be delighted. It's a pleasure to have you on board.
No. Pleasure's mine.
Well, let's get started.
I thought this book could help us identify trends and where people ended up after their teleportation.
My heart fluttered. Am I seriously feeling this way about a guy?
I think Master Fitz and I have gotten closer. But there's still a lot I don't know about him.
I've been meaning to ask, do you wear those sunglasses all the time?
Sunglasses... Oh, right. You mean these.
Yes, but I can't tell you why, sadly. Apologies.
It's okay. I have another one, though. What floor of the dorms do you live on?
Oh, well, that's a little odd, too. I actually sleep in the girls' dorm, since I guard Princess Ariel.
And that doesn't, like, cause problems or anything?
No, it's fine. I have permission. And besides, I would never cause problems for Her Highness.
Dorms are segregated by gender, but servants and slaves of the opposite sex are allowed in, with permission.
As a student, Fitz doesn't fall into either category.
But it's not surprising that the school would make an exception for Princess Ariel's guard.
So, I've noticed that you talk to me pretty normally.
Oh? What do you mean?
You seem to be known as a man of few words.
Uh, yes. In truth, I'm awfully shy.
I feel like he starts way too many conversations with me for that to be the case.
Oh, I also meant to ask, have you been casting without incantations since you were a child?
You're full of questions today, aren't you?
Yes. A long time ago, my master rescued me with voiceless magic, which is why I asked to start learning from him.
He's an amazing person, and I still look up to him to this day.
I had a master like that. I'd love it if I got to meet yours one day.
Yes, well, it would be hard to introduce you.
Yeah? Why do you say that?
His smile definitely makes my heart skip a beat or two.
I was sure I didn't swing that way.
Well, I have business with Princess Ariel.
Understood. I can't wait to work with you again.
Silent Fitz, man of mystery.
I don't know why he's so willing to help me, but I'm not fussed about unraveling that right now.
Following the man-god's advice brought us together, so maybe sticking with him will eventually lead me to my cure.
No reason to worry.
Master!
Please, teach me how to sculpt figurines!
Then there's this guy.
A figurine pervert who would be banned from your local comic shop.
Just look at you.
You put the natural world to shame.
I am prepared to get your own...
This man loves figures.
Loves them.
But hey, I can see where he's coming from.
I might have enjoyed a figure or two in my past life.
You gave me your word, did you not, Master?
Why must you refuse yet again to begin my instruction?
I didn't promise him, and I have been brushing up.
I just haven't wanted to make the time.
This isn't what I came here to do.
Xanobah, understand my tutelage will be strict.
Yes, Master. I'm ready.
Very well. You've proven your resolve.
I shall now impart the secrets of my art.
Thank you, sir!
And thus, our great figurine enterprise began.
Sorry.
So, blame yourself.
If only I were more skilled.
Well, hey. There's another way.
Yes! Teach me this other way, Master!
Okay.
For this, we'll try to use as little magic as possible.
Oh, what are we going to do with that?
We'll carve it up.
Chiseling, carving...
It's not any easier than using magic,
but it's primitive, tried and true.
People with no mana at all have been doing it forever.
Spectacular!
Master!
I believe that even I can learn this art!
Xanobah just isn't very good with his hands.
His supernatural strength makes delicate,
detail-oriented work something of a challenge.
It's too hard!
I can't do it!
I'll never be able to scum like you do, Master!
So, yeah.
That's what I was up to all of yesterday.
But you can already make figurines with magic?
Yeah.
See?
Are you kidding me?
That's amazing!
Nope, I can't do it.
That's not something your average caster can imitate.
I suppose it isn't.
And it's difficult to teach.
We also tried carving blocks of clay,
but you can imagine...
Yeah, he'd be too clumsy for that.
Right.
I don't know if it'll help,
but I heard something around the Osoran capital
that sounded like it might be a similar type of case.
A similar case to Xanobah, you mean?
Yes.
They wanted some personally crafted item,
but they lacked the talent and skill to do it themselves.
Okay.
How'd that person get around it?
Well, um,
if I recall,
they just got a slave to do it.
Oh.
Never would've crossed my mind.
I'll see how Xanobah feels about that.
Then maybe go to the market during our break next month.
Great.
Whatever you decide,
I hope it works out.
Is something wrong?
No, I just...
I have some time off, too.
Next break.
Oh, good.
You earned it.
Mm-hmm.
Uh...
Well, in that case,
would you care to join us?
That okay?
I wouldn't be intruding?
No, of course you wouldn't.
And I'll be happy to treat you to a meal
in exchange for all your advice.
All right.
I think I'll take you up on that.
I'm Fitz.
It's a...
Pleasure.
I am the Third Prince of the Chiron Kingdom.
My name is...
Xanobah!
Master Fitz is the one who proposed this solution for your benefit.
Show him proper respect.
Understood, sir.
I'm sorry.
It is a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Xanobah Chiron,
Third Prince of the Chiron Kingdom,
at your service.
Do forgive my indiscretion.
That's quite all right.
Really, please.
I take no offense, Your Highness.
Don't mind me.
I guess we ought to start moving then, huh?
Are you ready?
I see many fine displays.
Master, where shall we begin?
No idea.
I've never done this before.
Maybe just start by looking around.
Oh, wow.
So many of them are actually naked.
And so big.
I didn't know they got like that.
Spoken like a true virgin.
Yes.
Yes, I was one of you once.
And now...
Now I've got other things to worry about.
Are you used to seeing people like this, Rudeus?
Oh, I'm sure you'll get more comfortable with it once you gain some experience.
Sure, if you say so.
But wait, does that mean you have experience, then?
Master, these warriors are of no use.
We need to be looking for someone who's both magically gifted and naturally adept with their hands.
Okay, so who's known for their dexterity?
Maybe dwarves, I guess?
And, well, if you intend to tutor them in magic, I think you should pick a child who doesn't know any yet.
At all?
Not if you can help it, no.
It can make voiceless magic easier.
Oh, can it really?
And if you start learning to cast by the time you're about five years old, it will do wonders for your mana capacity.
What makes you say that?
Most people seem to believe that mana capacity is set at birth.
That's what the textbooks say, but anecdotally, my master's case and mine prove them wrong.
It can expand.
I knew it.
I always suspected.
But if I started casting around two or three, that would explain my mana pool for sure.
Well, if we know who we're looking for, we should try to find a merchant.
Hmm.
Yeah, we don't see dwarves of any age around here very often.
That might be a little hard to find for you.
If it helps, they don't have to be a dwarf.
They just need to be naturally dexterous.
But we're also teaching magic, so it's more important to find someone young enough to pick it up.
Ah.
Hey.
We do have one.
See that?
Six-year-old dwarf girl.
Looks like the whole family went into slavery to cover her parents' debts.
She's the only one left.
She's in pretty poor condition.
Malnourished, though feeding her regularly will fix that.
She only speaks beast guard, and she can't read or write but what six-year-old can.
Works for us.
Would you let us meet her?
There she is.
All right.
Come on.
If you want my professional opinion, I can't recommend her.
Rudeus.
Okay.
Master, what's the problem?
Just look at her.
She's in despair.
It's like she's lost all hope.
Or that she longs for death.
Oh.
Then you've seen such people before, I take it.
Why?
I used to.
All the time.
That's how I used to look.
Empty, helpless.
I knew it would never get better.
I just wanted to give up.
I can only do so much to save this girl.
I mean, sure we could buy her and take care of her and give her a job.
What kind of salvation is that?
It's probably not what she wants.
No one is going to save her by forcing her to do something against her will.
And if that's all I can offer her, I could at least ask if she wouldn't rather just...
...
Oh, my God.
All right, then. It's settled. That's enough. It doesn't have to be I want to live. I don't want to die is just fine for now.
Oh, Rudeus. What's her name? I don't know how to ask.
I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
Um, I don't want to die.
I don't want to die. I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
I don't want to die. I don't want to die.
Bizarre of the Holy Steel, then what?
Oh, of course. Dwarves don't get proper names until they turn seven, I think.
We are going to have to call her something, though.
Yeah, so why don't we pick out a name right now?
Something cute. She deserves something cute.
Xenobah, you got any suggestions?
Hmm. Yes. Julius.
Julius? Isn't that traditionally a man's name?
Yes. That was the name of my sweet baby brother who tragically died by my hand because I didn't quite realize my own strength.
Well, she is a girl, so maybe we should at least make it Juliet.
Very well. I have no objections.
A lovely name.
Lys Uosha. Uo Juliet.
Juliet.
Julie.
We decided that Julie would live with Xenobah and help him do whatever he does that he needs help with.
But during the day, I would teach her languages and incantationless magic.
And just like that, we had a brand new routine.
We'd all be making figures together in no time.
Until then.
And folks.
Literally sooner Earth.
It was during the beginning of your own life and rebirth.
So we are all various courses.
From the next wind, although the sum of our culture, might solve something else or goals,
as humans might be, once in a Patel, play in a guarantee.
Perhaps its butt in the same With the glasswind, grown as the value of each city
The best.
And all generations that tempts me im at home.
After it ends for a process, we die and thrive together in no time this country.
And the rest for us that爾, we're doing хорошie.
We know many wines ofапc enfocity.
Can you imagine that?
In the near 했습니다 project?
La-ya-la-ya-la